A Guide to the Purnell W. Choppin papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, Accession 1992:039 FA1073 FA1073
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Files, 6
  - NIH AI - 05600 09-13 (Box 10, Folder 16-17)
  - NIH AI - 05600 14-15 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - NIH AI - 05600 15-18 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - NIH Contract (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - NSF, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 21-22)
  - Frank Landsberger (Box 10, Folder 23-24)
  - Compans (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Dr. Eugenia Wang (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - MS Grant, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - MS Grant, 1974-1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - MS Renewal, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - NSF Renewal, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - NSF Grant - Renewal Application, 1973 November 30 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - NSF Grant - Renewal Application, 1976 July-1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - NSF Grant - Renewal Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - NSF Grant - Renewal, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - NSF, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Gordon Conference and Negative Strand (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Liquid N2 Notebook (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Committee Files, 7
  - Admissions Committee, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 15-17)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Confidential Material
  - AI-05600 19-23, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
  - AI-05600 19-23 Budget Adjustments (Box 11, Folder 20-22)
  - Cornell University Search Committee for Chairman (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - RU-Cornell-SKI Inter-Institutional Curriculum Committee (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Library Committee, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Professional Search for Clinical Research (Box 11, Folder 26-28)
  - Board of Scientific Consultants Memorial Sloan Kettering (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Committee on Life Sciences (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - RU Fellows Selection Committee (Box 12, Folder 5-17)
  - NIH Influenza Subcommittee, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 18-21)
  - Influenza Subcommittee, Houston, 1973 April 3-4 (Box 12, Folder 22-24)
  - Senate Meeting, 1969-1982 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Ad Hoc Committee (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
  - Molecular Biology Committee (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Promotion Committees (Box 13, Folder 7-9)
  - Academic Council, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - NSF - EM (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - AEC - First Year, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - AEC - Second Year, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - AEC - Third Year (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - AEC - Fourth Year (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Program in Viral Oncology (Box 13, Folder 16-19)
  - Kroc Foundation (Box 13, Folder 20-21)
  - American Association of Immunologists (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - American Society for Cell Biology (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - ASM-NIH Oversight Committee, 1978 January 14 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - ASM Nominations Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - ASM Virology Division (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - ASM Division Group IV (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - ASM, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - ASV Meeting University of California, 1986 June 22-26 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - ASV Meeting University of North Carolina, 1987 May-June (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - PNAS Instructions and Forms (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - PNAS Reviews (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - PNAS Communications (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
  - RU Press Editorial Board (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
  - Immunology Search Committee (Box 14, Folder 8-10)
  - University Fellows Committee (Box 14, Folder 11-16)
  - NIAID Virology Task Force (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - NIAID Virology Task Force 2 (Box 24, Folder 23-26)
  - LSU (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Penn State University (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Stanford (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - University of Washington (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Washington University (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - University of Wisconsin (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - University of North Carolina (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - University of Minnesota (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - University of Chicago (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - An Evaluation of the Role of Microbiological Criteria in Food and Food Ingredients, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - New Vaccine Development (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Board of Scientific Counsellors Meeting, 1975 October 30 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Issues and Priorities for New Vaccine Development - Draft Report, 1984 February (Box 25, Folder 4-6)
  - National Advisory Allergy and Infectious Diseases Council, 1985 January 24-25 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Institute of Medicine (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Various Domestic Diseases (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Issues and Priorities for New Vaccine Development, 1983 October 6-7 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Selecting Priorities for New Vaccine Development (Box 25, Folder 11-12)
  - Board of Scientific Counsellors Meeting, 1975 October 30 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Progress Report to Andrew W. Mellon Foundation - Cell Biology Research, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Virology - Reproduction of Myxovirus (Compans and Choppin) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Occasional Papers of the Rockefeller Institute (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
  - Role of Microbiological Criteria in Food and Food Ingedients (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Microbiological Role in Food (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Influenza Virus (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Guidelines for Grant Applications (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Institute of Medicine (Box 26, Folder 11-12)
  - Committee Meeting Additional Material, 1984 March 19-20 (Box 26, Folder 13-14)
  - Priorities for New Vaccine Development (Box 26, Folder 15-22)
  - Modern Dance of Death (Box 26, Folder 23)
- General Files, 8
  Scope and Contents
  Including but not limited to: Rockefeller University files, virology course work, lectures and seminars, as well as some journal files and committee, association and society records.
  - Virology Study Section and Virology Course Files, 1965, 1969-1970, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 17-32)
  - Virology Lectures, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Virology Course, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
  - 1965 Course II Lectures (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
  - Virology Course, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Virology Course, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Virology Course, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 8-10)
  - Virology Seminars, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Virology Seminars, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Virology Seminars, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 13-14)
  - Virology Seminars, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Virology Seminars, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Virology Seminars, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Virology Seminars, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Virology Seminars, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Virology Seminars, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Virology Seminars, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 21-23)
  - Virology Course, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 24-27)
  - Virology Course, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
  - Tutorial Sessions, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Virology Course, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 4-8)
  - Annals of Neurology (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Biochimica et Biophysica Acta (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Archives of Virology (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Journal of Experimental Medicine (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - American Journal of Medicine (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Infection and Immunology (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Cell (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Journal of Laboratory and Clinical Medicine (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Journal of Molecular Biology (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Journal of Immunology (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Nature (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Science (Cert. American Association for the Adv. Of Sci. Fellow) (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - The Medical Letter (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Journal of Infectious Diseases (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Journal of Supramolecular Structure (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Journal of General Virology (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Journal of Cell Biology (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Comprehensive Virology (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Journal of Virology (Box 16, Folder 28-29)
  - Biochemical Journal (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Biochemistry (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Journal of Clinical Microbiology (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Virology (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Macy Foundation Reviews - Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Sigma Xi (Box 16, Folder 36-37)
  - New York Academy of Sciences (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Harvey Society (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Practitioners Society (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - Infectious Diseases Society of America (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
  - China Exchange Program (Box 17, Folder 5-7)
  - China Trip Reports (Box 17, Folder 8-12)
  - China Visit, 1980 September (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
  - China Collected Papers (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
  - Wednesday Lab Talks (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Publications (Yearly List) (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Lab Report - Press, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Sep Report, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Annual Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Annual Reports, 1970-1974, 1975-1976, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Annual Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Annual Reports, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Major Accomplishments, 1970s (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - RU Catalog, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Institute Instructions and Announcements (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Accounting (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Animal Research Policy (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Air Rights - Subway (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Rockefeller University Archives (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Rockefeller University Calendar (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Computer Services (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Children's School (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller University Council (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  - Rockefeller University Development Program (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Energy (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Club (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Committees (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Faculty House (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Grant Fellowship Deadlines (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Graphic Services (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - NIH Grants - Information Forms (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Human Research Institutional Review Board (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Hospital (Box 18, Folder 15-18)
  - Housing Office, Abby (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Isotopes (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Lab Procedures Miscellaneous Instructions (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Lecture Committee (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Library (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Media (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Personnel (Box 18, Folder 25)
    Restricted - Personnel Material
  - Purchasing (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Plant Operations (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Recombinent DNA (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Retirements - Deaths (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Virology Course, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 30-32)
  - Virology Course, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 33-35)
  - Virology Course, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - RU Council, 1983 December 5 (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
  - Evenings at the Rockefeller University (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
  - Talks to Trustees and RU Council, 1971, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Flexner Colloquy (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Dinner - President House, 1985 January 17 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - RU-NYU Humanities Seminars (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - RU Admissions Committee, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Rufkin (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Connelly (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Leslie McKenzie (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Student Roster (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - MacArthur Foundation Parasitory Application (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
  - Indirect Cost Rate (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - State Education Department, Ph.D. Review (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
  - New York State Regents Plan (Box 19, Folder 20-21)
  - Plant Biology Survey (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Revson and Winston Foundations (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - cIcu (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - RU - Japan (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - RU - Karolinska (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - RU - Weizmann Institute (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Suntory Institute, 1984 September 7 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Fels Research Institute (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Seven Springs Center (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - VP Academic Program Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Graduate Medical Education Accreditation (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Questionnaires (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Status of Graduate Education (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Council for Chemical Research (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Council for Chemical Research - Celanese (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Manhattan Center High School (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - High School Science Program (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - National Beta Club (College Fact Chart) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - RU Alumni Organization (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Graduation (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Industrial Relationship (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Consulting Policy (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Patent, Copyright Policies (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Pew Scholar Program (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Experimental Medicine Pathology Seminars (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Postdoctoral Fellows (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - RU Screened Faculty and Fellowship Awards (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Hirschi (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Hirschi-Searle, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 15-16)
  - Junior Faculty Awards and Fellowships RU Competition (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - ASV President-Elect (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - SKI Virology Course, 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - RU Christmas Lectures (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Guide for Graduate Fellows (Box 20, Folder 21-23)
  - RU Cytology Course, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Graduate Fellows (Box 20, Folder 25-26)
  - Cell Biology (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - College Lectures (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - RU High School Biology Course (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Guidelines for Microbiological Labs (Box 20, Folder 30-32)
  - 25th Anniversary Convocation (Box 20, Folder 33-35)
  - Ad Hoc Committee (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - Academic Council, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
  - Academic Council, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Academic Council, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
  - Academic Council, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - University Fellows, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 11-14)
  - Parking (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Safety and Security (Box 21, Folder 16-19)
  - Shops (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Staff Benefits Insurance (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Student Affairs (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Travel Regulations (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Trustees (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Fellowship Information (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Rockefeller University News and Notes (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - FASEB Newsletter (Box 22, Folder 3-4)
  - Medicolegal (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - T. M. Rivers (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Library Committee (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
  - First Year Students, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Deans Office Budget (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Student Health (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - SRC (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Ph.D. Program (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Ph.D. Germany (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Student - Development Office (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - M.D. - Ph.D. Program (Box 22, Folder 16-17)
  - NSF Presidential Young Investigator Awards (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - M.D. - Ph.D. Site Visit - Grant 1984-1989 (Box 22, Folder 19-20)
  - Courses (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Student Advisory Committee (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Committee of University Industrial Relations (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Endowment and Contributor to Graduate Programs (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Deans Office Thesis Examinations (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Virology Committee (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Cell Biology Committee (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Virology Course Reports (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Cost of Education (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Development Office Case Statement (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Dreyfus Teacher Scholar Award (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Allen and Sinsheimer Awards, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Andrew Mellon Foundation Reports (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Neurosciences Foundation Reports (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Scientific Advisors Subcommittee, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Scientific Advisors Subcommittee, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Scientific Advisors Subcommittee, 1976-1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Scientific Advisors Subcommittee (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 7-9)
  - Senate Meetings, 1983, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Michael Heller (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Eugenia Wang (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Rodney Nichols (Box 23, Folder 13-14)
  - Joshua Lederberg (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
  - Dr. Edward L. Gershey (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Al Gold (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Michael Graves (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - William W. Hall (Box 23, Folder 20-21)
  - Dr. Otto Haller (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Roger P. Hand (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Anne M. Haywood (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Donald H. Harter (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Michael Heggeness (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - David Helfgott (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Garry Hoffman (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Kathryn Holmes (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Susan Abrahams (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Nicholas H. Acheson (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Larry Altsteil (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Dalius B. Briedis (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Elena Buetti (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Richard Compans (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Rise Cross (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Walter Doerfler (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Polly Etkind (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Bradley K. Evans (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Mark Kaplan (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Hans D. Klenk (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Robert Lamb (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Sany Lazarowitz (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - David Mertz (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - James J. McSharry (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Walter Mountastile (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Mark A. Pallansch (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Peter Prehm (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Chris Richardson (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Andreas Scheid (Box 24, Folder 17-18)
  - Jane V. Scott (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Lawrance Sturman (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Paula Traktman (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Laboratory Notes and Notebooks, 3
  - Polio and Guonidine on SV5 RNA Yield, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Hak Spinner, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous References, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Flu Antibody Studies (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - VSV - Prints (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - JMC Virus - Virus-like Particles (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Graphs, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Promyein on On-going SV5, RNA Protein in Presence of Polio plus Stimulation of Yield and RNA (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Cook Dowling (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Measle SSPE (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
  - Dr. Choppin - (Correspondence and Reports) (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
  - Scientific Information (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Lipids (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Sphingo Lipids (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Lee-Roseman (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Book I (primarily manuscripts and reprints) (Box 27, Folder 14-15)
  - Book II (primarily manuscripts and reprints) (Box 27, Folder 16-17)
  - Purnell W. Choppin Room 401 - Virology Lab Manual (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Choppin - Immunology Committee (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Dr. Purnell W. Choppin (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Persistent Infection (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Tam-Choppin - Virology Lab Manual (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Dr. Purnell W. Choppin (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Must be Acted Upon (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Flu Lipids - First Draft (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Notebooks on Gordon Conference, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Choppin - LSU School of Medicine - Disease Notebook (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Lab Notes - Original Rough Worksheets, 1957-1960 (Box 28, Folder 1-20)
  - Reference Guide - Influenza (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - NAS Award File I (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - NAS Award File II (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Virology - Reproduction of Paramyxoviruses (Box 28, Folder 24)